I'm just trying to give it momentum in many ways. Even if I'm about to make a mistake like that...
It's okay.
The new school leaders, a dance vocal group that has been attracting attention around the world, made their first appearance!
We also danced together with the much talked about "Adult Blue"!
You can't get enough of this kind of good stuff!
The Dumb Channel audience... we're going to stick out with our individuality and our freedom.
The New School Leaders are here!
New School Leaders, thank you very much!
Adult Blue's popularity is unbelievable!
It's suddenly here, isn't it? You're all so cool about it.
I love it!
I'm doing it all the time, at home and backstage.
I like it so much, I'd better stop.
Any tips? How to do it well.
Keep your hands and shoulders still, and move only your neck.
It's difficult. You're good. You're very good.
You have a good sense of rhythm.
Can I sing a little with you?
Five, six, seven, eight.
I don't want it anytime soon. I want it now. I'm longing for adult love.
It's more than meets the eye
Down in the blue buds
Adult blue!
Perfect!
Oh, no! I got the voice off!
I'm so happy!!!
What are the latest trends among the new school leaders?
A while ago, when I got excited...
Let's go! when we got excited.
I used to do that.
I'm just trying to give it a boost in a variety of ways.
I was like, "Okay, let's go! in a sense of "Let's go!
Let's go!
When do you do it, for example?
For example, when someone is about to
Or someone is about to slip up.
Or if someone is about to make a mistake...Even if you're about to make a mistake.
Okay! I want to do it! I want to do it! I want to!
You're right!
It's up, isn't it? It's up.
It lifts my spirits.
What was your most memorable experience at an overseas concert?
I've been to a lot of gigs overseas.
It's more open, isn't it?
It's not that they don't mind speaking out, it's more like their voice comes out before they even think about it.
It's like their voices come out before they think about it.
It doesn't have to be a cool cry.
Wow!
Hahahahahaha
Hahahahaha!
It's coming out! It's coming out! It's coming out!
It's coming out!
It's a case of "it's coming out!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
We decided to pretend to play that song.
The next song was the one with the hachimaki.
When you have a hachimaki, people who know the song will play it.
I wanted to say it was the night before the exam.
I wanted to say "The night before the exam", but when I was about to say it with hachimaki
The moment I was about to say it with the hachimaki, the audience said
The night before the exam!
Hahahahaha!
Very well.
I was about to say, "What are you going to say first?" but I ignored it and just let him die.
I felt like a loser.
You have your first arena solo show coming up in October.
It's going to be at the Tokyo Metropolitan Gymnasium.
We are going to perform at the Tokyo Metropolitan Gymnasium, and I think the gymnasium is very suitable for us.
I would like to fill the whole gymnasium with our power and passion.
But I'm not sure what we're going to do yet.
We haven't decided exactly what we're going to do or what the setlist will be yet, so we're still looking forward to it, even though we're still a little bit in the dark about it.
I'm looking forward to thinking about it!
Now, let's challenge the questions that were drawn in the "Dumb Gacha" game!Now, you will draw a dam gacha and try to guess the theme of the game!
Who will draw?
Yes!
23!
Have a good day!
Good night!
I'm going!
It's pink!
New school leaders dance gesture game!
Oh!
In this game, one of you will express a theme by dancing,
The rest of the members will try to guess what the theme is!
Sounds fun!
I'm going to participate in this one, too.
You will take turns to try 5 questions!
Yes!
Guess the theme!
Let's start the music!
Kaiten Sushi
What?
Huh?
Sushi Conveyor belt!
That's right!
Yikes!
I think it's funny that you can tell! Amazing!
The next challenger is Kanon-san!
Ah!
Bicycle?
No, a bike!
Oh, wait, that's hard!
Merry-go-round!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my God!
All this?
That's too much!Too awesome!
The next challenger was Miju!
New! Mermaid!
Mermaid! Mermaid! Mermaid!
Was it a dance?
The next challenger was Suzuka!
Lion.
What?
Facial? Poo?
Dog! Poo!
I don't know!
Born? Dinosaur! Dinosaur!
And finally, Rin!
Where shall we go?
Rice balls. Bamboo shoots.
Is it moving that fast?
What?
Shaky, shaky, shaky!
Power up!
Oh, um, Momotaro.
Oh, wow!
Wow!
I'm getting the Japanese call.
I see.
It's pretty easy.
He spoiled me a little bit.
Spoiled me.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is that you?
Yeah. Us?
We're too much.
I don't know if that's true.
Oh, great.
It's about time we did it again for the rest of our lives.
It's fun.
I want to do it again.
I want to go around the block.I'd like to go around the block.
It's going to be my hobby from now on.
We'll do it together, right?
Let's do it at the school.
Music News to keep you up to date on our guests
Our new EP is
The opening theme song for the drama "Lieutenant Daimajin
Majin And Adult Blue.
THE FIRST TAKE version of "Adult Blue" and more!
It contains 5 songs in total!
And our first one-man arena live will be held at Tokyo Metropolitan Gymnasium on Oct. 29th.
It will be held at Tokyo Metropolitan Gymnasium on October 29th!
Yes, please check it out!
Check in!
What song do you want to sing now?
The song I want to sing now is "Aim and Shoot" by Rinta Yamamoto!
Aim and Shoot is Rinta Yamamoto's energy!
It's great!
And we also covered it on our EP.
Please check it out too!
So, let's get to it!
Dumb Channel!
What does the word "demon" mean?
In Karaoke Dumb, we asked them to reveal the secret behind the new song "Majinin no Maa" (Demon's Demon)!
I see.
Gorgeous artists appear as guests!
Please subscribe to our Good Button Channel!
Hmmm...